Guide to the Peter H.L. and Edith Chang Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Liu, Duo-quan
    - Miao, Cheng-liu [also as Miao Ch’eng-liu] and Liu Duo-quan [also as Liu Tuo- chuan] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 4/3/[1937], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 43)
      [See Miao Cheng-liu [Box 4]]
    - Liu, Duo-quan To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 16/1/[1937], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 43)
      [Note: See Ma Zhan-shan [Box 4]; With 8 people listed: Ma Zhan-shan, Yue Xue-zhong, He Zhu-guo, Dong Ying-bin, Wang Yi-zhe, Miao Cheng-liu, Shen Ke and Liu Duo-quan]
    - Liu, Duo-quan To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 10/1/[1937], (5 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 03, Folder 43)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Liu Duo-quan, [n.p.] 19/[n.m.]/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 43)
      [See Yu Xue-zhong [Box 4]]
  - Liu, Feng-zhu
    - Liu, Feng-zhu To Peter H. L. Chang, Chungking 8/2/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 07.04)
  - Liu, Jin-wen
    - Liu, Jin-wen To Peter H. L. Chang, Guangxi 26/4/1993, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 07.05)
  - Liu, Ming-jiu
    - Liu, Ming-jiu To Peter H. L. Chang, [Shenyang] 5/12/1990, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 44.01)
    - Liu, Ming-jiu To Peter H. L. Chang, Shenyang 27/10/1993, (4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 44.02)
    - Liu, Ming-jiu To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 6/5/1996, (3 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 44.03)
    - Liu, Ming-jiu To Peter H. L. Chang, Shenyang 23/9/1996, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 44.04)
    - Liu, Ming-jiu To Peter H. L. Chang, Shenyang 18/1/1997, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 44.05)
    - Liu Ming-jiu To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 14/6/, 10/12 and 1996, (10 photos ) (Box 03, Folder 44)
      [See Photo [I-L.]]
  - Liu, Qi-guang
    - Liu, Qi-guang To Peter H. L. Chang, Taiwan 9/11/M35[1946], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 45.01)
    - Liu, Qi-guang To Peter H. L. Chang, Taiwan 20/8/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 45.02)
    - Liu, Qi-guang To Peter H. L. Chang, Taiwan 14/11/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 45.03.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Liu Qi-guang, Taiwan 19/11/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 45.03.02)
    - Liu, Qi-guang To Peter H. L. Chang, Taiwan 25/11/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 45.04)
  - Liu, Shao-tang
    - Liu, Shao-tang To Peter H. L. Chang, Taiwan 6/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 46)
      [See Media [Box 6, Folder 11.3]]
    - Liu, Shao-tang To Peter H. L. Chang, Taiwan7/8/1990, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 46)
      [See Media [Box 6, Folder 11 .3]]
    - Liu Shao -tang To Peter H. L. Chang, {n.p.} 1994], (New Year’s Card; 1 page letter signed, August 7, 1990; 1 page letter signed May 6 [n.y.] ) (Box 06, Folder 09.03)
    - Wang, Fu-shi To Liu Shao-tang, Taiwan 4/7/1990, (2 page, autograph letter signed (photocopy) ) (Box 06, Folder 08.05)
  - Liu, Yi-guang
    - Liu, Yi-guang To Peter H. L. Chang, [Taiwan] 3/10/[n.y.], (3 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 47.01)
    - Liu, Yi-guang To Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei 16/11/[n.y.], (5 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 47.02)
  - Liu, Zhe
    - Liu, Zhe [also as Liu Che ], Mo De-hui [also as Mo Teh-hui ], To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 26/3/[1937], (5 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 48.01)
    - Mo, De-hui and Liu Zhe To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 12/2//[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 48)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 14 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
  - Liu, Zhong-di
    - Liu, Zhong-di [also as Liu Chung-ti] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 49)
  - Liu, Zhong-pu
    - Liu, Zhong-pu [also as Liu Chung-p’u] To Peter H. L. Chang and Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 21/9/[n.y.], (4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 50)
  - Lu, Guang-ji
    - Lu, Guang-ji To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 29/1/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 51)
    - Lu, Guang-ji To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 10/1/[1937], (5 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 03, Folder 51)
      [Note: See Sun, Wei-ru ]
  - Luo, Wen-gan
    - Luo, Wen-gan [also as Lo Wen-kan] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Guangxi] 9/2/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 52)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, pages 5-6 [Box 1. Folder 1]]
  - Ma, Shou-li
    - Ma, Shou-li To Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei [n.m.]/1995, (5 page, printed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 09.04)
    - Ma Yi To Zhang Shou-fang, [n.p.] 14/4 [n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 10.04)
  - Ma, Zhan-shan
    - Ma, Zhan-shan [also as Ma Chan-shan],et al To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An ] 16/1/[1937], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 01)
      [See Ma Zhan-shan [Box 4]; With 8 people listed: Ma Zhan-shan, Yue Xue-zhong, He Zhu-guo, Dong Ying-bin, Wang Yi-zhe, Miao Cheng-liu, Shen Ke and Liu Duo-quan]
  - Mang, Da-ling
    - Mang, Da-ling To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 18/2/[n.y.], (1 page telegram ) (Box 06, Folder 07)
  - Mao, Ren-feng
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mao Ren-feng [also as Mao Jen-feng], [n.p.] 21/1/[n.y.], (1/2 page, autograph letter (draft) ) (Box 01, Folder 02)
      [See Meiling Soong Chiang [Box 1 Folder 12.4]]
    - Mao, Ren-feng To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 23/1/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 02.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mao Ren-feng, [n.p.] 12/4/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 02.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mao Ren Feng, [n.p.] March 5 [n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 37, Folder 03.04)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mao Ren-feng, [n.p.] 16/4/[n.y.], (1 page autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 02.02)
    - Mao, Ren-feng To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 17/4/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 02.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mao Ren-feng, [n.p.] 6/5/[n.y.], (1 page autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 02.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mao Ren-feng, [n.p.] 12/5/[n.y.], (1 leaf, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 02.03)
    - Mao, Ren-feng To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 15/6/[n.y.], (1 page, manuscript letter signed plus 1page list ) (Box 04, Folder 02.04)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mao Ren-feng, [n.p.] 26/7/[n.y.], (1 page autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 02.04)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mao Ren-feng, [n.p.] 3/8/[n.y.], (1 page autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 02.05)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mao Ren-feng, [n.p.] 24/10/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 02.05)
  - Marquis, Jeane T.
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Jeane T. Marquis, Taipei 22/11/1979, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
  - McCarthy, Doran C.
    - McCarthy, Doran C. To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, Nashville, Tennessee 19/3/1990, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 03)
  - Miao, Cheng-liu
    - Miao, Cheng-liu To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 10/1/[1937], (5 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 04, Folder 03)
    - Miao, Cheng-liu To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 16/1/[1937], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 03)
    - Miao, Cheng-liu [also as Miao Ch’eng-liu] and Liu Duo-quan [also as Liu Tuo-chuan] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 4/3/[1937], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 03)
      [ See Miao Cheng-liu [Box 4]]
  - Miller, Harry W.
    - Miller, Harry W. To Peter H. L. Chang, Taiwan 28/7/1955, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.21)
    - Miller, Harry W. To Peter H. L. Chang, In flight 14/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.21)
    - Tong, Holington K. To Harry Miller, Taipei 16/3/1961, (2 page, typed letter (copy) ) (Box 06, Folder 02)
    - Miller, Harry W. To Hollington K. Tong, [n.p.] 19/3/1961, (2 page, typed letter signed (copy) ) (Box 06, Folder 02)
    - Tong, Hollington K. To Harry W.Miller, Taipei 24/3/1961, (4 page, typed letter signed(copy) ) (Box 06, Folder 02)
  - Mo, De-hui
    - Mo, De-hui and Liu Zhe To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 12/2//[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 04)
    - Che, Jing [also as Ch'e Ching] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Iowa], 5/4/[n.y.], (5 page autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 05)
      [With photograph]
    - Mo, De-hui [also as Mo Teh-hui] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 19/12/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 04)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 15 [Box 1 Folder 1]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mo De-hui, [n.p.] 8/11/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 04.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mo De-hui, [n.p.] 23/1/[n.y.], (1 leaf. autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 04.01)
      [See Mo De-hui]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mo De-hui, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 04.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mo De-hui, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 04.01)
    - Mo, De-hui To Liu Yi-guang, [n.p.] 5/[n.m.]/[n.y.], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 04.02)
  - Montagliani, Ernie S.
    - Montagliani, Ernie S. To Peter H. L. Chang, Maidsville, W,Va 21/7/1964, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.22)
  - Monty [?]
    - Cory [?] To Monty {?}, Peitou, Taiwan 8/4/1973, (2 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 06, Folder 06.28)
  - Moore, Raymond S.
    - Moore, Raymond S. To Peter H. L. Chang, California 10/11/1960, (1 page, typed letter signed and 2page typed announcement ) (Box 06, Folder 02)
    - Tong, Holington K. To Raymond S. Moore, Taiwan 18/11/1960, (1 page, typed letter draft) (Box 06, Folder 02)
    - Moore, Raymond S. To Holington K. Tong, California 22/11/1960, (1 page, typed letter signed(copy) ) (Box 06, Folder 02)
  - Mu, Chao
    - Mu, Chao To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 21/2/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 07.06)
  - Nationalist Party Central Committee
    - Nationalist Party Central Committee To Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei 27/1/m40[=1951], (2 page, autograph letter ) (Box 06, Folder 16.01)
  - Ning, En-cheng
    - Ning, En-cheng [also as Ning En-Ch’eng] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 15/2/M35[1946], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 05.01)
    - Ning, En-cheng To Peter H. L. Chang, [California] 10/5/1994, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 05.02)
    - Ning, En-cheng To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 12/2/1996, (2 page, autograph letter signed, 1 page t.l. and 2 printed pages ) (Box 04, Folder 05.03)
    - Ning, En-cheng To Peter H. L. Chang, Palo Alto, CA 15/9/1997, (1 page, autograph letter signed and 1page faxed copy announcement ) (Box 04, Folder 05.04)
    - Pan, E-nian To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] [13/4/1937], [13/4/1937], (2 page autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 06)
  - Ning, Wu
    - Ning, Wu To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 19/2/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 07.07)
  - Northeast Benevolent Association in Greater Washington D.C.
    - North East Benevolent Association in Greater Washington D.C. To Peter H. L. Chang, Washington,D.C. 1/6/1990, (3 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 05.08)
  - Northeast Benevolent Association in Taiwan
    - Northeast Benevolent Association in Taiwan To Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei 22/5/ n. y., (1 page, typed letter signed and envelope with 3calling cards ) (Box 06, Folder 05.03)
  - Northeastern University
    - Northeastern University, Shenyang: May 1, 1995, (1 invitation card and 1 page photocopy of name list ) (Box 35, Folder 01.07)
    - Northeastern University, Shenyang: July, 1995 3 page a. l. s. photocopy (Box 35, Folder 01.08)
    - The Alumni General association of the Northeastern University, Shenyang: July 14, 1995 4 page t. l. s. (Box 35, Folder 01.08)
    - Northeastern University, Shenyang, China: November, 1993, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 35, Folder 01.04)
  - Pan, Hui-yu
    - Pan, Hui-yu To Peter H. L. Chang, Tainan 8/9/1997, (1 page, autograph letter signed and photograph ) (Box 06, Folder 01.06)
  - Qiao, Yun-peng
    - Qiao, Yun-peng [also as Ch’iao Yun-peng] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Ann Arbor Mich.] 8/4/[1937], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 07)
  - Qin, Shi-xian
    - Qin, Shi-xian [also as Ch’in Shih-hsian] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 10/3/M26 [1937], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 08)
  - Qin, Xiao-yi
    - Qin, Xiao-yi To Peter H. L. Chang, Taiwan 3/7/[1987], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 09)
  - Qiu, Qin
    - Qiu, Qin To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 28/5/1998, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 09.01)
      [See Northeastern University [Box 33]]
  - Qiu, Yong-he
    - Qiu, Yong-he [also as Chiu Yung-he] To Peter H. L. Chang, Los Angles 18/5/[1937], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 10)
  - Radio Bible Class
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Radio Bible Class, [Taiwan] 4/6/1966, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 11.02)
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Radio Bible Class, [Taiwan] [n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 05, Folder 11.02)
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Radio Bible Class, [Taiwan] 1/1/1977, (2 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 05, Folder 11.02)
  - Rose, Royce
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Royce Rose, Taipei 10/5/1984, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
  - San Yu Tang Committee
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To San Yu Tang Committee, [n.p.]17/5/[n.y.], (6 leaf, autograph letter draft) (Box 06, Folder 10.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To San Yu Tang Committee, [n.p.] 18/9/1931, (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 10.01)
    - Hu Ruo-yu To San Yu Tang Committee, [n.p.]7/3/1947, (4 page, typed letter signed and 2 page of lists ) (Box 06, Folder 10.01)
  - Sasakawa
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mr.. Sasakawa, [n.p.] March 22 [n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 37, Folder 03.04)
  - Seminary External Education Division (SEED)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Seminary External Education Division (SEED), Taipei 2/10/1980, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To SEED, Taipei 14/5/1982, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To SEED, Taipei, 19/5/1983, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To SEED, Taipei7/7/1983, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To SEED, Taipei 8/3/1984, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To SEED, Taipei [n.d.], (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Seed, Taipei 23/8/1966, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
  - Shao, Li-zi
    - Shao, Li-zi [also as Shau Li-tzu] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Shanghai] 14/2/M26[1937], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 11)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, pages 20-21[Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Shao, Li-zi To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 6/5/M36[1947], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 11)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 23 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Shao Li-zi, [n.p.] 19/4[n.y.], (1 p autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 11)
      [See Mei-ling Soong Chiang [Box 1 Folder 13.1]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Shao Li-zi, [n.p.] 16/5[n.y.], (1 leaf autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 11)
    - Shao, Li-zi To Mo De-hui, [n.p.] 2/[n.m.]/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 11)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 22 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
  - Shen, Ben-wei
    - Shen, Ben-wei To Peter H. L. Chang, Hawaii,[n.d.]/1/1991, (1 autograph card signed ) (Box 06, Folder 08.03)
  - Shen, Dan
    - Shen, Dan [Shen Tan] To: Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 6/9//M36 [1947], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 12)
  - Shen, Hong-lie
    - Shen, Hong-lie [also as Shen Hung-lie] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Nanking] 15/2/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 13)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 40-41[Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Shen Hong-lie [also as Shen Hung-lie] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 28/n.m./n.y., (2 page telegram ) (Box 04, Folder 13)
      [See Box 6, Folder15]
  - Shen, Ke
    - Shen, Ke To H. L Chang, [n.p.] 16/1/[1937], (2 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 04, Folder 14)
    - Shen, Ke To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 10/1/[1937], (5 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 04, Folder 14)
  - Shi, Bing-yan
    - Shi, Bing-yan [also as Shih Ping-yan] To Peter H. L. Chang, Shanghai 9/1/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 15)
  - Shi, Yuan-quan
    - Shi, Yuan-quan To Liu Yi-guang [also as Liu Yi-kuang], [Kai-Yang] 21/5/M31[1942], (2 page manuscript [telegram] ) (Box 04, Folder 16)
      [ See Dai Li [Box 3] ]
    - Shigeo Nishimura To Peter H. L. Chang, Osaka 9/1/1995, (4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 36-1)
  - Song, Chu-yu
    - Song, Chu-yu To Peter H. L. Chang, Taiwan 14/12/1990, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 17)
  - Song, Li
    - Song, Li To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 4/11/1993, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 18)
  - Sormani, Egbert J.
    - Sormani, Egbert J. To Peter H. L. Chang, New York 13/12/1966, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.23)
  - Soong, T. A.
    - T. A. Soong To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] June 12, 1954, (1 mini greeting card ) (Box 37, Folder 03.04)
  - Sun, Ke
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Sun Ke [also as Sun K’e], [n.p.] 17/5/[n.y.], (1 leaf autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 19)
  - Sun, Wei-ru
    - Sun, Wei-ru [also as Sun Wei-ju] et al To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An ] 10/1/[1937], (5 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 04, Folder 20)
  - Sun, Xue-ying
    - Sun, Xue-ying To Peter H. L. Chang, Qiqiha’er 19/11/1989, (1 page, autograph letter signed and two postcards dated 20/11/1989 ) (Box 06, Folder 01.07)
  - Tai, Ma Li
    - Tai, Ma Li To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 22/3/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [n.y.] [n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai Ma Li To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [n. p.] 5/5/59, (1 greeting autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Twinem, Paul DeWitt and Tai Ma Li [Mrs.. Twinem] To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 15/8/1959, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, Taipei 17/5/1966, (1 autograph card signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 19/12/1966, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, Taiwan 20/3/1967, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 25/5/1968, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 26/6/1968, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 9/8/1968, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.]7/12/1968, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 9/1/1969, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 13/2/1969, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, Taiwan 14/6/1969, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 18/6/1969, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 6/2/1970, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 5/5/1970, (1 autograph card signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 11/10/1970, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, Florida 9/11/1970, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Tai Ma Li, [n.p.] 1/9/1971, (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 12/11/1971, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 12/2/1972, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 8/3/1972, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 5/11/1972, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, Taiwan 2/12/1972, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] Resurrection Day/1972, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai Ma Li ( Mrs.. Paul De Witt Twinem) To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, Shihilin [n.p.] 5/3/1973, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 16/7/1973, (1 calling autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 02.01)
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Tai Ma Li, Taipei 29/3/1975, (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 9/4/1975, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Tai Ma Li, [n.p.] 2/5/1975, (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 8/3/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 8/3/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, Shihlin [n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.y.] [n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 05, Folder 01)
    - Tai, Ma Li To Edith Chao Chang, [n.y.] [v.d.], (11 miscellaneous notes ) (Box 05, Folder 02.02)
  - Tang, Xian-ke
    - Tang, Xian-ke To Peter H. L. Chang, Beijing 14/8/1991, (4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 08.04)
  - Tang, Zong
    - Tang, Zong [also as T’ang Tzong] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 24/7/[1947], (1 page, autograph letter signed plus 1page medicine list ) (Box 04, Folder 21)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Tang Zong, [n.p.] 4/9/[1947], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 21)
  - Tao, Xiao-zhou
    - Tao, Xiao-zhou To Peter H. L. Chang, Shenyang [n.d.]/[n.m.]/1998, (1 page, autograph letter signed (on back of newspaper article from Shenyang Daily, December 10, 1998) ) (Box 06, Folder 05.04)
    - Soong, T. A. To Hollington K. Tong, [n.p.] 22/11/1960, (1 page, typed letter (copy) ) (Box 02, Folder 05.03)
  - TongYi Luntan Zazhe
    - Tongyi Luntan Zazhe [United Forum] To Peter H. L. Chang, Beijing 28/2/1998, (1 page, typed letter (photocopy) ) (Box 06, Folder 09.05)
  - Tong, Yu-chi
    - Tong, Yu-chi [also as T’ung Yu-ch’ih] To Peter H. L. Chang, Lincheng 3/3/[n.y.], (4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 22)
  - Tue, William
    - Tue, William To [Peter H. L. Chang], Utah 18/6/[n.y.], (1 typed card ) (Box 06, Folder 06.24)
  - Tunghai University
    - Tunghai University To Peter H. L. Chang, Taichung, Taiwan: March 30, 1993, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 35, Folder 03)
  - Underwood, Felix J.